华纳兄弟电影公司
时代华纳集团
拉特派克制片公司
漫画
神奇女侠
WONDER WOMAN
过去我总想着拯救世界
I used to want to save the world.
这个美丽的星球
This beautiful place.
可那时我涉世未深
but I knew so little then.
这是一片奇妙非凡的土地
It's a land of magic and wonder.
太值得被珍爱
Worth cherishing in any way.
但你越是靠近
But the closer you get,
就越能看清  黑暗在蠢蠢欲动
the more you see the great darkness shimmering within.
而人类
And mankind?
人类又是另外一回事了
Mankind is another story altogether.
韦恩集团
知道真相后要作出怎样的抉择
What one does when faced with truth
比你想象中要困难很多
is more difficult than you think.
我也是摸爬打滚才学会这个道理
I learned this the hard way.
那已经是很久以前的事了
A long long time ago.
现在的我
And now,
也不再是过去的我了
I'll never be the same.
谢谢
merci.
我找到了那张照片
也许有一天你会告诉我你的故事
你好  戴安娜
Hello, Diana.
-你好啊  戴安娜  -你好
- Hello, Diana. - Hello.
戴安娜
Diana!
快回来
Come back!
-她还不错  -很不错
- She looks very good. - Very good.
她呢
How is she?
很好
Good.
-继续操练  -好的
- Keep working. - I will.
戴安娜
Diana!
戴安娜  我看到你了
Diana, I see you.
你要去哪  慢点
Where are you going? Slow down!
你好  母亲
Hello mother.
你今天怎么样
How are you today?
快回去上课
Let's get you back to school,
不然这个老师也不教你了
before another tutor quits.
可你不觉得我应该开始训练了吗
Don't you think it's time to start my training?
安提俄珀觉得我已经准备好了
Antiope thinks I'm ready.
是吗
Does she?
我可以开始教她些基本的招式了
I could begin showing her some things.
她起码要有保护自己的能力
She should at least be able to defend herself.
谁会伤害她
From whom?
入侵者
In the event of an invasion.
我有史上最伟大的战士和她带领的部队
Isn't that why I have the greatest warrior in our history
这还不够吗  将军
leading an entire army, General?
我祈祷永远不会有战乱
I pray they will never come to where she has to fight.
但你要知道  是蝎子就会蛰咬
But you know, a scorpion must sting.
-是狼就会扑杀  -她还是个孩子
- A wolf must hunt. - She is a child.
这岛上唯一的孩子
The only child on the island.
就让她当一个孩子吧
Please let her be so.
可是  母亲
But, mother...
不许训练
There will be no training.
我保证会小心的  好吗
What if I promise to be careful?
该睡觉了
It's time to sleep.
我不用剑  行不行
And if I didn't use a sword?
会战斗不代表你就是个英雄
Fighting does not make you a hero.
那就只用盾  不用尖锐的兵器
Just the shield then, no sharp edges.
戴安娜  你对我来说是这世上最宝贵的
Diana, you are the most precious thing in the world to me.
我渴望有个小生命
I wished for you so much,
所以亲手用泥土塑造了你
so I sculpted you from clay myself.
并恳求宙斯赋予你生命
And begged Zeus to give you life.
你以前跟我讲过这个故事
You've told me this story.
所以今晚我要给你讲个新的故事
Which is why tonight I'll tell you a new one.
关于亚马逊人的历史和我们的战争年代
The story of our people and my days of battle.
太好了
Yes!
听完你就会明白  战争有多么可怕
So you will finally understand why war is nothing to hope for.
很久以前  世界初始
Long ago, when time was new,
一切历史都还没有发生
and all of history was still a dream.
众神统治着世界
The gods ruled the earth.
宙斯则为众神之首
Zeus king among them.
他创造了一种将被神统治的生物
Zeus created beings over which the Gods will ruled.
以他为原型打造
Beings born in his image,
公平善良  强壮  充满激情
fair and good, strong and passionate.
宙斯将他们称作"人"  人类天性善良
He called his creation "Man". And mankind was good.
但宙斯的儿子却对他们心生嫉恨
But Zeus' son grew envious of mankind,
想方设法摧毁他父亲的杰作
and sought to corrupt his father's creation.
他就是阿瑞斯  战争之神
This was Ares, the God of War.
阿瑞斯用嫉妒和怀疑荼毒人们的心灵
Ares poisoned man's hearts with jealousy and suspicion.
让他们自相残杀
He turned them against one another.
令战争肆虐各地
And war ravaged the Earth.
因此  众神创造了我们亚马逊人
So, the gods created us, the Amazons.
让我们用爱意感化人们的心灵
To influence men's hearts with love,
让世界重现和平
and restore peace to the Earth.
确实有过一段短暂的和平
And for a brief time, there was peace.
却很快被打破了
But it did not last.
你的母亲亚马逊女王  发起了反抗
Your mother, the Amazon Queen, led a revolt
让我们族人摆脱了奴役
that freed us all from enslavement.
宙斯率领众神来保护我们
When Zeus led the gods to our defence,
可他们却相继被阿瑞斯杀掉
Ares's killed them one by one,
最后只剩下宙斯一个人
until only Zeus himself remains.
宙斯拼尽全力阻止阿瑞斯
Zeus used the last of his power to stop Ares,
发动致命一击  战争之神不得不撤退
striking such a blow, the god of war was forced to retreat.
但宙斯明白
But Zeus knew,
终有一日阿瑞斯会卷土重来
that one day Ares might return
完成他的使命
to finish his mission.
那将是场无休止的战争
An endless war
人类将在自相残杀中灭亡
where mankind would finally destroy themselves,
我们也将难逃厄运
and us with them.
因此  宙斯给我们留下了一件武器
So Zeus left us a weapon.
一件足以杀死神的强大武器
One powerful enough to kill a god.
宙斯用最后一口气  创造了这座岛屿
With his dying breath, zeus created this island,
将我们与世隔绝
to hide us from the outside world.
这样阿瑞斯就无法找到我们
Somewhere Ares could not find us.
从此一切都平息了下来
And all has been quiet ever since.
我们感恩众神赐予我们这样一座天堂
We give thanks to the gods for giving us this paradise.
那弑神者呢
And the God Killer?
弑神者
The God Killer?
那件足以杀死神的强大武器
The weapon that is strong enough to kill a God.
能让我看看吗
Can I see it?
众神赐予了我们许多宝物
The gods gave us many gifts.
总有一天  你都会知道的
One day, you'll know them all.
这座高塔就是我们的藏宝地
This great tower is where we keep them.
弑神者
The God Killer.
好漂亮
It's beautiful.
谁会使用它呢
Who would be wield it?
我希望它永远不会被派上用场
I pray it will never be called to arms.
只有最勇猛的人才配拥有它
But only the fiercest among us even could.
那个人不是你  戴安娜
And that's not you, Diana.
懂吗  你很安全
You see? You are safe,
你完全不必担心
and there is nothing you should concern yourself with.
你总是不够自信  戴安娜
You keep doubting yourself, Diana.
-不  我没有  -你有
- No, I don't. - Yes. You do.
我没有
No, I don't.
你比自己想象的还要强大
You're stronger than you believe.
你根本不知道自己有多大能量
You have greater powers than you know.
-如果不努力些...  -戴安娜
- But if you don't try harder... - Diana!
受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
没有  母亲  我没事
No, Mother, I'm fine.
-我只是在...  -训练
- I was just... - Training.
看来没有人把我这个女王放在眼里
It seems I'm not the revered queen I should be.
我的亲妹妹都能违抗我的命令
Disobeyed, betrayed by my own sister.
不  母亲  都怪我  是我让
No, mother. It was me. I asked her...
带她回宫殿
Take her to the palace.
快走吧
Off you go.
你让我别无选择  希波吕忒
You left me no choice, Hippolyta.
如果她不会战斗  那就是你的失职
You neglect your duty, if she cannot fight.
你说的是遥不可及的事
You speak of a time that may never come.
也许他不会回来  也许他受伤后就死了
He might never return. He could have died from his wounds.
阿瑞斯还活着
Ares is alive.
你心底里跟我一样  都能感受得到
You feel it as I do, in your bones.
他何时再现只是时间问题
It's only a matter of time before he returns.
她越强大  就越容易被他找到
The stronger she gets, the sooner he will find her.
希波吕忒  我跟你一样爱她
Hippolyta, I love her as you do.
但只有这样才能真正保护她
But this is the only way to truly protect her.
那你对她的训练就要比任何人都要严厉
You will train her harder than any Amazon before her.
严厉五倍
Five times harder,
严厉十倍
ten times harder.
直到比你还强大
Until she's better than even you.
但一定不能让她知道她的身世
But she must never know the truth about what she is,
以及她的使命
or how she came to be.
认真点
Harder.
你可比这强  戴安娜
You are stronger than this, Diana.
再来
Again.
永远不要放松警惕
Never let your guard down.
你以为战斗是公平的吗
You expect the battle to be fair.
战斗没有公平可言的
Battle will never be fair.
安提俄珀
Antiope!
别起来
Please don't.
你流血了
You're bleeding.
-对不起  -别过来  戴安娜
- I'm sorry. - Wait, Diana.
我到底干了什么
What had I done?
对不起
I am sorry.
怎么这么大的雾
Where did this fog come from?
在那  前进
There. Go forward.
他在那
There he is!
那个飞行员  我看到他了
The pilot! I can see him.
你是男人
You are a man.
是啊
Yeah. I mean...
难道我看着不像男人吗
Do I not look like one?
这是在哪
Where are we?
天堂岛
Temiscira.
什么
What?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是好人  他们是坏人
I'm one of the good guys and those are the bad guys.
什么
What?
他们是德国人  快走  我们得离开这
The Germans. Come on, we need to get out of here.
-德国人  -戴安娜
- The Germans? - Diana!
离她远点
Step away from her now.
弓箭手准备
Ready your bows!
她们有枪的  对吧
They have guns. Right?
开火
Fire!
射击
快跑
Come on!
趴下
Stay down!
盾牌
Shield!
不
No!
No.
不  不  安提俄珀
No. No. Antiope.
安提俄珀
Antiope.
戴安娜
Diana.
是时候了
The time has come.
你必须
You... you must...
什么  安提俄珀  你说什么
What? What, Antiope?
弑神者
God Killer!
-戴安娜  快去...  -去哪
- Diana, go... - Go where?
-去哪  -去...
- Where? - Go...
不  不要  不
Please no. No, no!
-不  -安提俄珀
- No! - Antiope!
不
No!
-你  -不  母亲  不要
- You. - No mother, no.
不要这样  母亲
No mother.
他帮我一起攻击了入侵者
He fought at my side against the invaders.
谁会背叛自己人
What man fights against his own people?
我跟他们不是一伙的
These aren't my people.
那你为什么穿着他们的衣服
Then, why do you wear their colors?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you that.
快说
You need to tell us now!
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
这也不能告诉你
I can't tell you that either.
现在就杀了他  以防后患
We should kill him now and be done with it.
如果他死了
If he dies,
我们就无从得知他们是谁以及为何而来
we know nothing about who they are and why they came.
我
My...
我是史蒂夫·特雷弗上尉
Name is Captain Steve Trevor,
飞行员  美国远征军
Pilot, American Expeditionary Forces.
编号8141921
Serial number 8141921.
我要说的就是这些
That's all I ever need to...
我被派遣至英国情报机构
Assigned to British intelligence.
这到底是什么东西
What the hell is this thing?
真言套索能让你说出真相
The lasso of Hestia compels you to reveal the truth.
可它为什么这么烫
But it's really hot.
抵抗是毫无意义的  只会徒增痛苦
It is pointless and painful to resist.
你在执行什么任务
What is your mission?
你们不知道现在自己的处境有多危险
Whoever you are, you are in more danger than you think.
你在执行什么任务
What is your mission?
我是个...
I am a...
间谍
I'm a spy.
我是间谍  我是间谍
I'm a spy. I'm a spy.
英国情报机构得到消息
British intelligence got word
德国陆军上将  鲁登道夫
that the leader of the German Army Gen. Ludendorff.
要前往奥斯曼帝国的
Would be visiting a secret military installation
一个秘密军事基地
in the Ottoman empire.
我伪装成德国飞行员与他们一同前往
I posed as one of their pilots and flew in with them.
根据情报  德军已溃不成军
According to our intel, the Germans had no troops left.
没有资金  也没了军需品
No money, no munitions of any kind.
但我们的情报是错的
But our intel was wrong.
德军让土耳其人为他们制造炸药
The German had the Turks building bombs for them.
不光是炸药  还有新式武器
And not just bombs, new weapons.
秘密武器
Secret weapons.
该武器是由鲁登道夫手下头号变态
Invented by Ludendorff's chief psychopath,
伊莎贝尔·丸博士负责研发
Dr. Isabelle Maru.
前线士兵称她为"毒药博士"
The boys in the trenches called her "Doctor Poison".
这么说不是没有道理的
And for good reason.
根据我的判断  如果丸博士研发成功
From what I could tell if Dr Maru was able to complete her work.
上百万人会死去  战争就会永无休止
Millions more would die. The war would never end.
我的任务是暗中观察并汇报  仅此而已
I was there to observe and report nothing more,
但我不得不采取行动
but I, I had to do something.
我相信我肯定能让毒气渗入面具
I know I can get the gas to pass through the mask.
也就是说  我还需要时间
Which is, I need more time.
很遗憾  博士  我们没时间了
Unfortunately, Dr. We don't have more time.
这项研究
This work, this...
抓住那个人
Get that man!
在那
There!
如果我能把这些笔记
If I can get these notes back
及时送到英国情报部门
to the British intelligence in time,
就能挽救数百万人的性命
it could stop millions more from dying.
战争就会停止
It could stop the war.
战争  什么战争
War? What war?
就是战争
The War.
能结束一切的战争
The war that end all wars.
4年
Four years,
27个国家
27 countries,
2500万人死去
25 million dead.
士兵和平民
Soldiers and civilians.
无辜百姓
Innocent people.
妇女和儿童惨遭屠杀
Women and children slaughtered.
他们的家园被洗劫  烧毁
Their homes and villages looted and burned.
所用的武器  残忍程度...
Weapons far deadlier than you can...
无法想象
Ever imagine.
这是我从未见到过的惨状
It's like nothing I've ever seen.
仿佛世界末日就要来临
It's like the world's gonna end.
我们要放走他吗
Should we let him go?
好让他带更多的人来这里吗
And risk him bringing more men to our shores?
我们不能一直拘留他  女王大人
We can not hold him forever, my queen.
母亲  请听我说
Mother, excuse me.
那男人说了那么多  这一定是阿瑞斯干的
But after everything the man said, this must be Ares.
你在说什么  戴安娜
What are you talking about, Diana?
抱歉  参议员
Forgive me, Senator,
但那人说这是场无休止的战争
but the man called it a war without end.
已经有数百万人死去了
Millions of people already dead.
他从未看过这种惨状
Like nothing he's ever seen.
只有阿瑞斯才能干出这样的事
Only Ares could do such a thing.
不能就这么放他走  我们要跟着他去
We can not simply let him go. We must go with him.
我决不会派我们的人去打他们的战
I will not deploy our army and leave the scare defences
留着天堂岛无人镇守
to go and fight their war.
这不是他们的战争
It's not their war.
宙斯创造出来的人类是正义
Zeus created man to be just,
智慧  强壮  富有激情的
and wise, strong and passionate.
那只是个故事  戴安娜
That was a story, Diana!
有很多事你还不懂
There is much, you do not understand.
人类很容易堕落
Men are easily corrupted.
没错  但那一切都是阿瑞斯所为
Yes, but Ares is behind that corruption!
是阿瑞斯怂恿德国人发动战争
It is Ares who has these Germans fighting.
阻止战争之神是我们的使命
And stopping the God of war is our fore ordinance.
作为亚马逊人  这是我们的职责
As Amazons this is our duty.
但你跟我们这些亚马逊人不一样
But you're not an Amazon like the rest of us.
所以你什么都不要做
So you will do nothing.
身为女王  我不允许
As your queen I forbid it.
奇怪了
Strange.
是你救了他吗
Is it true you saved his life?
谁告诉你的
Who told you that?
他说的
He did.
我没看到你进来
I didn't see you come in.
是不是
Would you say you are a...
你们男人都长这个样子
A typical example of your sex?
我...
I am...
要高于平均水准
above average.
那是什么
What's that?
这是个...
It's a...
是块手表
It's a watch.
手表
A watch?
没错  是手表
Yeah, it's a watch.
看时间用的
Tells time.
我父亲送给我的
My father gave it to me.
这块表曾随他出生入死
Went through hell back with him.
现在到了我手里  还好它还在走
Now it's for me. Good thing it's still ticking.
它有什么用
What for?
能告诉你时间
Because it tells time.
什么时候该吃饭  睡觉  起床  工作
When to eat, sleep, wake up, work.
你让这个小东西指挥你做事情吗
You let this little thing tell you what to do?
是啊
yeah.
能问你几个问题吗
Can I ask you some questions?
-这是哪里  -天堂岛
- Where are we? - Temiscira.
你说过了  我是想问  这是哪
No, I got that before, but I mean. Where are we?
这是什么地方  你们是谁
What is this place? Who are you people?
为什么水是这样
Why does the water do that?
你为什么连手表都没见过
How come you don't know what a watch is?
你为什么英语说得这么好
How can you speak English so well?
我们会说几百种语言
We speak hundreds of languages.
我们是促进人类和平共处的桥梁
We are the bridge to a greater understanding between all men.
好吧
Right.
有句话我还没来得及说
I didn't get a chance to say this...
谢谢你把我从水里救了上来
Earlier, but thank you for dragging me out of the water.
谢谢你
Thank you.
在海滩上帮我们战斗
For what you did on the beach.
所以说
So...
你是来放我走的吗
You are here to let me go?
我试过了  但我说了不算
I tried, but it's not up to me.
我甚至还让他们派我和你一起去
I even asked them to send me with you.
或者亚马逊的
Or anyone.
任意一个人
In Amazon.
亚马逊人
The Amazons.
The Amazons?
保护世界是我们的神圣使命
It is our sacred duty to defend the world.
我也想去
And I wish to go.
但我母亲不允许
But my mother will not allow it.
其实
Well...
不能怪她
I can't say I blame her.
这场战争的走向
The way this war's going...
我也不想让我在乎的人靠近战场
I don't wanna let anyone I care about near.
那你为什么想回去
Then why do you want to go back?
应该没人"想"回到战场吧
I don't think "want" is the word, right?
但总得试一试
I guess I got to try.
我父亲曾经告诉我
My father told me once he said,
"要是你发现这世界上有什么事不对
"If you see something wrong happening in the world,
"你要么袖手旁观  要么有所作为"
"you can either do nothing, or you can do something."
我已经袖手旁观过了
And I already tried nothing.
这一身不错
Nice outfit.
谢谢
Thank you.
我告诉你怎么离开岛
Now I'll show you the way off the Island,
你带我去找阿瑞斯
and you'll take me to Ares.
说定了
Deal.
我就坐它走吗
I am leaving on that?
是我们
We are.
我们就坐它走吗
Yeah, we're leaving in that?
你会开船吗
Do you not know how to sail?
我当然知道
Of course I know how to sail.
我怎么会不知道  只是
Why wouldn't I know how to sail? It's just...
很久没开了
It's been a while.
我要走了  母亲
I am going, mother.
无辜的人不断死去  我不能坐视不管
I can not stand by while innocent lives are lost.
若世上无人抵抗阿瑞斯  那我必须去
If no one else will defend the world from Ares, then I must.
我必须去
I have to go.
我知道
I know.
至少我知道我拦不住你
Or at least I know I can not stop you.
有那么多
There is so much...
那么多你不明白的事
So much you do not understand.
我明白的够多了
I understand enough.
我愿意为那些
That I'm willing to fight for those
无法保护自己的人而战
who cannot fight for themselves.
就像你曾经那样
Like you once did.
你知道  如果你选择离开
You know that if you choose to leave,
可能就回不来了
you may never return.
我留下来又有什么用呢
Who will I be if I stay?
这属于我们历史上最伟大的战士
This belonged to the greatest warrior in our history,
我们敬爱的安提俄珀
our beloved Antiope.
保证你配得上它
Make sure you're worthy of it.
我会的
I will.
在人类的世界要小心  戴安娜
Be careful in the world of men, Diana.
他们不值得你去拯救
They do not deserve you.
你是我的挚爱
You've been my greatest love.
今天
Today,
你成了我最大的悲痛
you are my greatest sorrow.
你有告诉她吗
Should you have told her?
她知道得越多  他就会越快找到她
The more she knows, the sooner he will find her.
我们还有多久到战场
How long until we reach the war?
战场  哪一个
The war, which part?
法国西线战场
The Western Front in France is
从阿尔卑斯山到北海  长达四百多英里
400 miles long, from the Alps to the North Sea.
那就去战斗最激烈的地方
Where the fighting is the most intense then.
你带我去  我肯定能找到阿瑞斯
If you take me there, I'm sure I'll find Ares.
战争之神阿瑞斯
Ares as in the God of War?
找到他是我们的职责
The God of war is our responsibility.
只有亚马逊人能打败他
Only an Amazon can defeat him.
用这把剑
With this.
一旦我打败他
And once I do,
战争就会结束
the war will end.
你的劲头我很欣赏
I appreciate your spirit,
但这场战争
but this war is,
是一个烂摊子
It's a great big mess.
你我都没什么办法
And there's not a whole lot you and I can do about that.
我们可以回伦敦
I mean, we can get back to London,
找找能改变局势的人
and try to look for men who can.
我就是那个人
I'm the man who can!
等我找到并打败阿瑞斯之后
Once I find and destroy Ares,
德军就能摆脱他的影响
the German armies will be freed from his influence,
他们会回归善良  世界会变好
they will good men again and the world will be better.
好吧
Great.
等着瞧
You will see.
你干什么
What are you doing?
我以为你想
I thought maybe you wanna
睡一会
get some sleep.
那你呢  你不睡吗
What about you? Are you not sleeping?
一般男人都不睡觉吗
Does the average men not sleep?
不  我
No, I...
不  睡  但是我们不和
Yes, we sleep. We just don't sleep with a...
你们不和女人睡
You don't sleep with women?
不  我是说  也睡
No, I mean, I do, I sleep with... I sleep with...
我和女人睡
Yes, I do.
但除非
But out of the...
结了婚
confines of marriage.
不然
It's just...
连想都不该想
Not polite to assume, you know?
"结婚"
"Marriage"?
你不知道吗  也对  你们也不用
Marriage! You haven't heard... Yeah, you don't have to...
两个人走到神父面前
You go before a judge,
发誓要相爱  尊敬  珍惜彼此
and you swear to love, honor and cherish each other,
直到死亡将你们分开
until death do you apart.
他们会彼此相爱至死吗
And do they love each other till death?
不常有
Not very often, no.
那他们为什么这么干呢
Then why do they do it?
我不知道
I have no idea.
你不能跟我一起睡  除非
So you can not sleep with me unless...
你真想的话  我跟你睡  我在那睡
I sleep with you if you want. I'll sleep right there.
还有很大地方
There is plenty of room.
好吧  只要你不介意
Then fine, if you don't mind.
-不  你说了算  -我跟你睡
- No, it's up to you. - I'll come and sleep with you.
好
Okay.
在我们那里  我不算是普通人
Where I come from, I'm not considered average.
当间谍什么的
You know... Being a spy...
一定要有一定的
you must show a certain amount of...
实力
vigor.
你之前没见过男人吗  你父亲呢
Have you never met a man before? What about your father?
我没有父亲
I have no father.
我母亲用泥土塑造了我
My mother sculpted me from clay,
宙斯赋予我生命
and I was brought to life by Zeus.
那敢情好
Well that's neat.
抱歉
Sorry.
在我们那里
Where I come from,
孩子的诞生过程不一样
babies are made differently.
你指的是生殖繁衍吗
You refer to reproductive biology.
-没错  -我知道
- Yes, yes. - Yeah, I know.
我都知道
I know all about that.
我指的是那个  还有别的
I mean I refer to that and other things.
肉体的欢愉
The pleasures of the flesh.
你知道吗
Do you know about that?
克利欧[历史之神]批评现世欢愉的十二卷我都读过
I've read all 12 volumes of Clio's criticism on earthly pleasures
十二卷呢
12?
你就没随身带上一两本吗
Didn't you bring any of those with you?
你不会喜欢的
You would not enjoy them.
我不知道  也许会呢
I don't know. Maybe.
你肯定不喜欢
No you wouldn't.
为什么
Why not?
书最后得出结论
They came to the conclusion
要完成生殖过程必须有男人
that man are essential for procreation,
但若是想要获得欢愉
but when it comes to pleasure,
可以没有
unnecessary.
不
No.
晚安
Goodnight.
要多久我们才能投入战斗
How long until we're operational?
两天  长官
Two days, sir.
我们今晚就行动  上尉
We'll have it up tonight, Captain.
长官  将士们没吃东西也没睡觉
Sir, the men have had no food, no sleep.
你觉得我吃了睡了吗  上尉
Do you think I have had any food or rest, captain?
你听见我找借口了吗
Do you hear me making excuses?
没有
No.
你的手下软弱又自满
Your men, they are weak and complacent.
早就忘了敌人随时都可能进攻
We've let them forget for an attack can happen at any time.
从任何地方发起进攻
from any corner!
我们来提醒他们一下
So let's you and I remind them.
好吗
shall we?
-博士  -将军
- Doctor. - General.
进展如何
Progress?
还不行
Not enough.
结束了  将军
It is over, General.
德国要投降了
Germany is giving up.
冯·兴登堡已经建议皇帝签停战协约了
Von Hindenburg has recommended the Kaiser sign the armistice.
我们没时间了
We have run out of time.
皇帝一见到最新武器
As soon as the Kaiser sees the newest weapon,
他就不会签了
he will not sign the armistice.
但没有笔记本
But without my notebook...
我们会拿回你的笔记本的
We will get your book!
我信的是你  不是它
It is you that I believe in, not it.
我知道你的本事  你会成功的
I know what you can and will succeed.
你天生就是干这个的
It is what you're put on this earth to do.
我昨晚突发奇想
So I'm seeing, it come to me last night.
另一种气体
A different type of gas.
给你的
For you.
可以强化你的体能
To restore your strength.
我知道了  我知道了
I have got it! I have got it!
如果它跟我想的一样
And if it's what I think,
那将会
it's going to be,
很可怕
terrible.
早上好
Morning!
我们很走运  有人带我们一程  省了不少时间
We got lucky. We caught a ride, we make some good time.
欢迎来到亲切的伦敦
Welcome to jolly old London!
好丑
It's hideous.
是啊  不是所有人都喜欢它
Yeah, it's not for everybody.
-早上好  亲爱的  -美人
- Good morning darling. - What a babe.
不
No!
先生们  别乱看  非常感谢
Gentlemen, eyes to yourself. Thank you so much.
快走
Come on!
他们为什么牵着手
Why are they holding hands?
可能因为他们在一起了
Probably because they're together.
不  我们没在一起  不是一个意思
No. We're not together, I mean, in that way.
这边
This way.
去战场
To the war!
严格来说  战场是那边
Technically, the war is that way.
但我们得先走这边
But we gotta get this way first.
我们去哪
And where are we going?
我们得把笔记本交给上级
We gotta get this notebook to my superiors.
不  我放你走  你带我去找阿瑞斯
No. I let you go. You take me to Ares.
-我们说好的  史蒂夫·特雷弗  -是啊
- We made a deal, Steve Trevor. - Yeah.
说好了就是保证了
And a deal is a promise.
保证过就不能食言
You know promises are unbreakable.
天啊  该死  好吧
Boy! Damn it, alright.
先跟我来  我们把它送过去
Come with me first to deliver this,
然后给你买张票
and then we'll give you a ticket,
去战场
to the war.
说好了
Deal?
-走吧  -戴安娜
- Let's go. - Diana.
你干什么
What are you doing?
你不能这么做  因为你没穿衣服
You can not do that because you're not wearing any clothes.
我们去买衣服吧
Let's go... Let's go buy some clothes.
这些女人打仗时穿什么
What do these women wear into battle?
她们不
They do not...
小孩
A baby!
不  别碰小孩
No, no babies.
别摸他
No babies.
他不是泥土做的
That's not made out of clay.
过来
Come on.
戴安娜  求你了
Diana! Please.
谢天谢地  你没死
Thank God! You're not dead!
太好了
Hurray!
接到你电话之前我真以为你死了
I did think you're dead till I got your call, you know?
他消失了好几个星期  一点消息都没有
He has been gone for weeks.. Not a single word.
非常不像他的风格
Very unlike him.
我自我介绍一下  我叫埃塔·坎蒂
I am introducing myself. I'm Etta Candy.
我是史蒂夫·特雷弗的秘书
I am Steve Trevor's secretary.
秘书是什么
What is a secretary?
我什么都做
Well, I do everything.
他让我去哪我就去哪  让我干什么我就干什么
I go where he tells me to go and I do what he tells me to do.
在我们那儿  这叫奴隶
Where I am from, that's called slavery.
我真喜欢她
I really like her.
真棒  女士们先请
Fantastic. Ladies after you.
我真喜欢她
Oh I do, I like her.
确实跟奴隶差不多  但我们薪水还不错
I did that's all feel like that, except the pay is rather good.
我们是另外一种体力劳动
We've bought our work. For a second way.
这是你们国家的铠甲吗
Is this what passes armor in your country?
-铠甲  -是时尚
- "Armors". - It's fashion.
能收紧小肚子
Keeps our tummies in..
为什么要收紧
Why must you keep them in?
没有小肚子的女人才会这么问
Any woman without tummy would ask that question!
保守  但又不失趣味
Conservative, but not entirely unfun.
起码穿上试试
Try it on at least.
好吧
Very well.
不
No!
快来
Come on!
女人穿着这个怎么打仗
How can a woman possibly fight in this?
打仗
Fight?
我们有我们的手段
We use our principles.
这样能争取到投票权
I mean, that's how we are gonna get the vote.
虽然我也不反对动用一点武力
Although I am not opposed to engaging in a bitter fist
在迫不得已的时候
should the occasion arise.
很好
Lovely.
好痒  我喘不上气了
It's itching. It's choking me.
反正总有人喜欢
Can they blame it?
埃塔
Etta.
她在哪
Where is she?
她在试第226件
She's trying out number 226.
坎蒂女士  目的是让她别那么
Ms. Candy, the whole point was to make her look less
显眼
distracting.
可以吗
May I?
真的吗  眼镜
Really? Specs?
以为戴上它就不是你见过的最美的人了
Suddenly she's not the most beautiful woman you've ever seen?
好多了
Better.
这样行不通
Yep, that's not gonna work.
把剑放下  戴安娜
Please put the sword down, Diana.
戴安娜
Diana!
我自己来
Let me try by myself.
你先请  先生
After you, sir.
埃塔
Etta.
我在办公室等你
Why don't I meet you back at the office?
这个交给我保管
And meanwhile, I'll take this for safekeeping.
不  我觉得不行
Oh no, I don't think so.
你得把剑放下  戴安娜  求你了
You gotta put the sword down, Diana. Please.
-跟你这一身不搭  -一点都不搭
- It doesn't go with the outfit. - Not at all.
先把剑放下
Put the sword down, first of all.
答应我  你会用生命保护它
Promise me you'll protect it with your life.
好  才不
Yes... No.
你可以相信她  给她
You can trust her. Just hand that over.
-盾牌  -盾牌也给她
- Shield. - And the shield to her.
拿好了吗  谢谢  埃塔
You got it? Thanks, Etta.
这很容易
This is easy.
好了
There we go.
怎么了
What is it?
希望没事  快走
Hopefully, nothing. Come on.
-史蒂夫  我们在躲什么  -快来
- Steve, why are we hiding? - Come on, come on!
特雷弗上尉
Captain Trevor.
我相信你身上肯定藏着
I believe you have something
鲁登道夫将军的东西
that is the property of Gen. Ludendorff.
坏蛋的惯用口吻
It's the bad guy convention.
把丸博士的笔记本交出来
Give us Dr Maru's note book.
我把它放哪来着
Where I put that thing?
往后站
Stand back!
要不还是你来
Or maybe not.
算你倒霉
Tough luck.
你还有什么没展示给我看的吗
Is there anything else you wanna show me?
你想去哪
Where do you think you're going?
抱歉  但你显然是被阿瑞斯控制了
I'm sorry, but you're clearly under Ares' control.
-戴安娜  -让我来帮你
- Diana. - Let me help you get free.
阿瑞斯在哪
Where will I find Ares?
他死了
He's... he's dead.
氰化物
Cyanide.
待着别动  我马上回来
Stay here. I'll be right back.
拜托  先生们
Come on! Gentlemen, please!
让他说
Let him speak!
谢谢  先生们
Yes thank you, gentlemen.
德国这个国家无比傲慢
Germany is an immensely proud nation.
他们不会投降的
They will never surrender.
想结束这场战争
Now look. The only way to end this war...
上校  借一步说话
Colonel, I need to talk to you outside.
让世界重获和平
and restore world peace.
唯一的办法就是谈判
It is to negotiate...
签停战协定
an armistice.
有个女人
There's a woman.
她在这干什么  让她出去
What is she doing here? Get her out.
让她出去
Ger her out.
抱歉
Sorry.
她是盲人  迷路了
Blind sister, she got lost.
应该是那边
I think it's right there I guess.
眼下我们唯一的目标
Our only aim at this time
一定要不惜一切代价
must be to achieve peace
争取和平
at any cost!
为什么不听他讲话  他在谈论和平
Why you been not hearing speech? He is talking of peace.
不是现在
Not right now!
特雷弗  你到底在想什么
Trevor, what the hell were you thinking
居然把女人带到这里来
bringing a woman into the counsel?
我带回来的情报时间非常紧急
The intel that I brought back is time sensitive.
这是一本丸博士的笔记本
This is one of Dr. Maru's notebooks.
管它是什么本
Notebook or notes...
我们得把它送去解密
We need to get it to Cryptography.
而且我需要立刻和各位将军汇报这件事
And I need a immediate audience with the generals.
你不能随意闯进这里
You do not just barge in here.
上校请恕我直言  我所看到的那些
Sir with all due respect. What I saw in my...
将会改变这场战争的走向
Will change the course of war.
特雷弗上尉
Captain Trevor!
我听说在一次行动中失去了你
I heard we lost you in one of your mission,
看来你是死里逃生了
and here you are, back from the dead,
还带来了一位朋友
and I see you brought a friend.
我对冒昧闯入的行为深感抱歉
My deepest apology for interruption sir.
无须道歉
No, non sense.
谢谢这位女士
Thanks to this young woman,
房间终于能安静下来
the room was finally quiet enough
听我讲几句话了
for me to get a few words in.
我是帕特里克·摩根  乐意效劳
Sir Patrick Morgan, at your service.
戴安娜  我是天堂岛的
Diana, princess of the...
普林斯  她叫戴安娜·普林斯
"Prince". Diana Prince.
她是
She is...
我
And I..
我们
Are...
是同事
Working together.
她帮助我带回了这本笔记
She actually helped me bring this notebook back here.
这笔记来自丸博士的实验室
That through Dr Maru's lab.
我想里面写的内容
I think the information it contains inside
会改变这场战争的走向
will change the course of the war, Sir.
我的天
My God.
-毒药博士的吗  -是的
- Dr. Poison herself. - Yes, Sir.
太好了
Yes.
有趣
Intriguing.
还有什么别的情报吗
Any further intelligence?
很遗憾  解密部门没破解出来
Sadly not, sir. Cryptography had no luck.
这笔记像是由两种语言组成
It seems like it's a mixture of two languages,
但他们并未解出是哪两种语言
but as if they failed to determine which two languages.
土耳其语和苏美尔语
Ottoman and Sumerian.
这个房间里肯定有其他人也知道吧
Surely someone else in this room knew that.
这个女人是谁
Who is this woman?
她是我的
She is my...
秘书
Secretary, sir.
她懂土耳其语和苏美尔语
And she can understand Ottoman and Sumerian?
她是位能力出众的秘书
She's a very good secretary.
如果这位女士能看懂
Sir, if this woman can read it,
我们得听听看她怎么说
we should hear what she has to say.
那就听吧
Yes very well.
这是个配方
It's a formula,
一种新型气体
for a new kind of gas.
芥子气  用氢取代了硫
Mustard gas, hydrogen based instead of sulfur.
用氢取代了硫
Hydrogen based...
防毒面具挡不住氢基气体
Gas masks will be useless against hydrogen.
笔记上说他们计划在前线
The book says, they plan to release the gas...
释放这种气体
At the front?
什么时候
When?
这没说
It doesn't say.
等下  什么前线
Wait. In "front" of what?
长官
Sir,
这就是我们要找的证据
that is the evidence we need.
得找到她们在哪里制造这种气体
You have to find out where they are making that gas.
然后将这种气体燃烧殆尽
You have to burn it to the ground.
彻底摧毁
Destroy it.
鲁登道夫最近一次出现是在比利时
Ludendorff was last seen in Belgium.
我们不能明目张胆地把军队派去
We can't be seen in sending troops
被德国占领的比利时
into German-occupied Belgium,
特别是他们打算投降的节骨眼上
as we are negotiating their surrender.
我亲眼看到过这种气体
Sir, I have seen that gas with my own eyes.
一旦它被使用  两边的人都会被杀死
If it is used, it will kill everyone on both sides.
他们都会丧命
They will all die.
是的  这就是士兵的职责  上尉
Yes, that's what soldiers do, Captain.
派我去  只需要给我一些后勤上的支持
Send me in with some logistical support.
至少给我一个机会
At least give me the chance
去摧毁鲁登道夫的计划
to take out Ludendorff's operation myself.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
我在这个节骨眼上可不想节外生枝
I can't introduce rogue elements this late in the case.
长官  我能
Sir, I can take...
此时此刻
Now more than ever,
停战协定才是最重要的事情
the armistice is off paramount importance.
我们必须要谈判  协定必须被签署
It must be negotiated it must be signed.
这是停止战争最好的方法
It is the best way of stopping the war.
上尉  你什么都不许做
Captain, you will do nothing.
这是命令
And that's an order.
好的长官
Yes sir.
我明白了
I understand, sir.
我不明白
I don't!
戴安娜  我知道这令人困惑
Diana, I know this is confusing.
-我不困惑  简直不可理喻  -这个女人是谁
- It is not confusing! It's unthinkable! - Who is this woman?
她和我一起的  她站在我们这边
She is with me, she is with us.
我才不是和你一起的
I'm not with you!
你在知情的情况下牺牲那么多的生命
You would knowingly sacrifice all those lives,
就像他们的命没有你值钱似的
as if they mean less than yours.
-戴安娜  我们出去说  -就像他们无足轻重
- Diana, let's talk about it outside. - As if they mean nothing?
在我的家乡
Where I come from,
将军才不会像懦夫一样躲在办公室里
generals don't hide in their offices like cowards.
-够了  -他们和士兵并肩作战
- That's enough! - They fight alongside their soldiers.
他们和士兵在战场上出生入死
They die with them on the battlefield!
-够了  抱歉  -你应该感到羞耻
- That's enough! My apologies. - You should be ashamed.
-对不起  -你应该感到羞耻
- My apologies. - You should be ashamed.
戴安娜
Diana...
你们都应该感到羞耻
All of you should be ashamed!
请慢一点
Please slow down!
这就是你的领导
Is that your leader?
他怎么能这么说  你能相信吗
How could he say that? Believe that?
还有你
And you!
你的工作就只是把那本笔记给他们吗
Was your duty to simply give them a book?
不是
No!
你没有坚持你的立场  你没有反抗
You didn't stand your ground. You didn't fight.
因为我们没有办法改变任何事
Because there was no chance of changing anything.
这可是阿瑞斯  他是绝不可能谈判
This is Ares. It's not going to allow negotiation,
也不可能投降的
nor a surrender!
你曾说上百万民众都会因此丧命
The millions of people you talked about, they will die.
我们会去的
We are going anyway!
你是说你在说谎吗
You mean you were lying?
我是个间谍  这是我的工作
I'm a spy! That's what I do!
我怎么知道你现在不是在跟我说谎呢
How do I know you're not lying to me right now?
我会带你去前线
I'm taking you to the front.
我们极有可能会死的
We are probably gonna die.
这是个糟糕的主意
This is a terrible idea.
我们得找些帮手
We're gonna need reinforcements.
这些人就是帮手吗
These are the reinforcements?
是的
Yep.
你确定他们是好人吗
Are these even good men?
相对而言
Well, relatively.
就算是在非洲也没见过这样富到流油的
Even in Africa gentlemen, we haven't seen such luxuries.
而到了我们手里
The luxury that we have now is like
就是赚钱赚到手软
we can't stop making money!
我和我叔  还有一位王子
So my uncle, the Prince, and I...
等一下  哪位王子
Wait, which prince is that?
我决定宽恕你的不敬
I decided to extend your profanity...
说真的  哪位王子
But seriously, which prince?
苏丹的  安哥拉的还是哪个国家
Hey, Sultan, Angora, Next Kashmir...
我们能借一步说话吗
...Can we talk for a minute?
先生们  恕我失陪一会儿
Gentlemen, excuse me one second.
-这里是酒馆  -你这家伙
- A bar... Well, a pub. - You buck...
我在跟这帮家伙吹牛皮呢  你来干吗
I've been racing those peacock all night, and you've...
我的天啊  天哪
Oh my goodness, gracious.
这简直是艺术品
That's a work of art.
萨米尔  这是戴安娜  戴安娜  这是萨米尔
Sameer, Diana. Diana, Sameer!
你好戴安娜  请叫我萨米
Hi, Diana. You can call me Sammy please.
"萨米"
"Sammy".
萨米尔  我奉劝你别那样做
Sameer, I wouldn't... do that if I were you.
萨米尔是顶尖的卧底
Sameer is a top undercover man.
他巧舌如簧  也跟你一样会说多种语言
He can talk the skin off a cabbage many ways as you can.
他看起来好像没有那么厉害
我看你也差不多
你的眼神和你的笑容一样温柔
而你的眼神
看起来好像想要什么东西
我还会说中文 小姑娘
但你能用古希腊语背诵苏格拉底的名言吗
你们终于结束了
Oh, you're done.
查理在哪
Where is Charlie?
在那儿
Voila!
至少这个查理拳头还可以
At least this Charlie is good with his fists.
那不是查理
That's not Charlie.
这才是查理
That's Charlie.
史蒂夫
Steven!
愿上帝保佑你
May god grow a flower upon your head son.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
你刚刚为什么打架
So what were you fighting about?
我不小心拿错了他的杯子
I mistook his glass for mine.
失误在所难免
That happens.
这个人根本不是战士
This man is no fighter.
查理是个专业的狙击手
Charlie is an expert marksman.
意思是他打枪很准
Means he shoots people.
从远距离射击
From very far away.
他们都不知道怎么死的
You never know what hit 'em.
看不到他们的脸怎么知道自己打的是谁
How do you know who you kill if you can't see their face?
我不知道  这反而更好了
I don't. Trust me it's better that way.
你的战斗毫无荣誉可言
You fight without honor.
谁给我的荣誉买单
Who gets paid for honor?
所以这次是什么工作  老板
So, what's the job, boss?
最多两天
Two days tops.
需要准备物资还有通行证前往比利时
We need supplies and access to Belgium.
这趟下来多少钱
What is the going rate?
最好是个好价钱
Better be a good pay.
情况是这样的
Yeah, well, here's the thing.
这趟行程很短
I told you it will be quick.
然后你会收获很多东西
And there's a lot to be gained by this.
这是为了崇高的事业
It's for a great cause,
自由
freedom,
友谊
friendship,
结束战争  友谊
ending the war, friendship...
-所以你没钱  -没有
- Okay, You have no money. - No.
现在我唯一想要的 就是印着你美丽脸庞的照片
你不需要照片
我和你们一起去
什么
What?
什么意思
What is this?
我们将把她送到前线
We're gonna drop her up front!
-送她去  -是的
- "Dropping her off"? - Yeah.
问题是  我才不会为了救其他人
Question sweetheart, I am not gonna get myself killed
就牺牲我自己
helping every last human.
-我拒绝  -原来你这小偷在这
- That's NO, I mean. - Here's the little thief now!
我既害怕又兴奋
I am both frightened and aroused.
-你们在这儿  抱歉我来迟了  -帕特里克长官
- Oh here they are! Sorry I'm late. - Sir Patrick!
是啊  我刚想和你们说呢
Yes, that's what I was gonna mention.
帕特里克长官
Sir Patrick.
坐吧  先生们  普林斯小姐
No, no, Gentlemen, sit. Ms. Prince, sit.
我猜你们在谋划什么事情
I assume you are here planning something,
这事会让你们上军事法庭  或是没命
that's going to get you either court martial or killed.
我猜  你是来阻止我们的
And I assume, you are here to stop us.
不是
No.
恰恰相反
Not at all in fact.
你看
Well, look.
我也曾经是个年轻人
I was an younger man once.
如果身体够硬朗  我也会做一样的事
Had I been in better health, and I might do the same.
你们做的事情非常光荣
It's very very honorable thing you're doing.
所以
Therefore,
我是来帮忙的
I am here to help.
当然是私下的
Unofficially, of course.
你们的计划是什么
What's your plan?
如果还有别的武器厂  找到一个毁一个
If there's another weapon's facility, find it and destroy it.
还有对付鲁登道夫和丸博士
Along with Ludendorff and Maru.
如果是这样  为了避免怀疑
In that case, to allay suspicion,
美丽的埃塔女士
our charming Etta
可以在我的办公室指挥这次行动
could run the mission from my office.
"指挥"
"Run"...
还有
Also.
这些应该够用几天的了
There is enough here for a few days.
谢谢您
Thank you sir.
乐意之至
You're very welcome.
你们多多保重
Take great care all of you.
祝你们好运
And good luck.
祝平安
Health!
新鲜的冰淇淋
Fresh ice-cream.
小姐  想来个冰淇淋吗
Miss, would you like to buy an ice cream?
-我吗  -你饿了吗
- Me? - You hungry?
是的
Yes.
谢谢
Thank you.
八便士  先生
Eight pence please, sir.
给你  不用找了
There you go, keep the change.
谢谢您  先生
Thank you very much sir.
-你在干嘛  -太好吃了
- What you doing? - It's wonderful!
-你应该感到非常骄傲  -谢谢您
- You should be very proud. - Thank you very much!
你应该感到非常骄傲
You should be very proud.
我们有很长很长的路
We have a long way
很长的路要走
A way to go
我也想在这摆个小摊
I hope I got niches here.
酋长还指望着我们天黑前能到呢
The chief's expecting us before dark.
酋长
Chief?
一个走私犯
Oh yeah. A smuggler.
非常有名
Very reputable.
骗子  杀手  又来个走私犯
A liar, a murderer, and now a smuggler.
太好了
Lovely.
小心  我要伤心了
Careful, I might get offended.
我没说你啊
I wasn't referring to you.
是吗
Really?
我为了卧底假装别人的身份
I wanna recover from pretending to be somebody else.
我在海滩上打死人  还偷笔记本
I shot people on your beach and stolen a notebook.
骗子  杀手和走私犯  你还跟我走吗
A liar, murderer and smuggler. You still coming?
这太惨了
It's awful.
这就是我们在这儿的原因
That's why we're here.
这种气体真要人命
The gas will kill everything.
什么样的武器才会让无辜的人受害
What kind weapons kills innocents?
在这场战争里
In this war,
每一种都是
every kind.
你没出席会议  将军
You were absent at the counsel meeting, General.
我看到你背着我在谈停战协定
I see you are negotiating the terms armistice without me.
-代表皇帝  -是你坚持的
- On the Kaiser's behalf. - On your insistence.
哪怕有点信心  我们都能轻松赢得胜利
We could easily win this war if only you had a little faith.
我们没有信心
We don't.
食物短缺
There are shortages of food,
药物和弹药都不足
meds and ammunition.
每耽误一刻  就有上千德国人牺牲
Every hour we delay costs thousands of German lives.
只要再发动一次攻击  世界就是我们的了
One attack and the world could be ours.
我的化学家
As we speak, my chemistry...
我们反对你和你的
We stand against you and your...
女巫
Witch.
鲁登道夫  够了  再过24小时
Ludendorff, enough! 24 hours from now,
这场战争就结束了
this war will end.
它结束了
It is over.
对你来说是结束了
It's over for you.
对你们来说都结束了
It is over for all of you..
但是防毒面具是没用的
But the mask won't help.
他们不知道啊
They don't know that.
走吧
let's go!
是时候给皇帝展示展示了
Time to stage a demonstration to the Kaiser!
你迟到了
You're late.
为了躲避偷袭  酋长
Avoid sneak attack, chief!
你怎么样
How are you?
-很高兴见到你  -大块头
- Good to see you pal. - Big mike.
-很高兴见到你  -太棒了
- Good to see you. - Yes!
很高兴见到你我的朋友
Good to see you my friend.
美人
Yaa beauty!
这是谁
Who is this?
我叫戴安娜
And I am Diana.
你从哪找到她的
Where did you find her?
她找到了我
She found me.
-我从海里捡到他的  -这是个很长的故事
- I plucked him from the sea. - Well. It's a long story.
你不用现在讲
You don't have to talk about that right now.
这是什么
What's there?
给德国人的英国茶叶
British tea from the Germans.
给英国人的德国啤酒
German beer for the British.
给两边的埃德加·赖斯·巴勒斯的小说
And Edgar Rice Burroughs novels for both.
还有枪
And guns!
祝我们得到自己想要的
Well. May we get what we want.
祝我们得到自己需要的
We get what we need.
祝我们永不会罪有应得
But may we never get what we deserve.
好奇怪的雷声
Strange thunder.
德国野战炮
German 77's.
相当于一支大枪
Guns big ones.
那边就是前线了
It's the front out there.
-像傍晚的浓雾  -所以你为了什么而战
- The evening haze. - So, who do you fight for in this war?
我不战斗
I don't fight.
那你是来这边做生意的了
You're here for profits then?
也没别的地方待了
No better place to be.
所以你就来到了战场上  还不效忠任何一边吗
Nowhere better to be than in a war where you don't take a side?
我无处可归
I have no where else.
上一次战争夺去了我的一切
The last war took everything from my people. We have nothing left.
至少在这
At least here,
我是自由的
I'm free.
是谁夺走了这一切
Who took that from your people?
美国佬
His people.
别去
Do not go.
别过去  别过去
Don't go in there. Do not go!
伙计们  别过去
Do not! Guys, No!
不要过去
Don't go in there.
你安全了
You are safe.
现在没事了  你还好吗
You are safe. Are you okay?
闭嘴  你个婆娘
Shut up, you woman!
少大惊小怪的
Stop making a fuss!
天哪
God!
他撞鬼了
He sees ghosts.
你会着凉的
Hey, you're gonna get cold.
谢谢你
Alright there.
别介意查理说的话  他不是故意的
Don't worry about Charlie. He doesn't mean any, alright?
他们为什么要伤害动物
These animals, why are they hurting them?
因为他们跟我们一样
Because they need to move quick!
-要赶路  -但这么做不对
- Like us! - But this is not the way.
我可以帮助他们
I could help them.
没时间了  快走吧
There is no time. Come on, woman!
妈妈
Mama!
那个人受伤了
That man, he's wounded.
你帮不了什么忙的  戴安娜
There is nothing you can do about it, Diana.
我们不能停下来
We must keep moving.
这是什么
What is this?
这就是你让我带你来的战场
You wanted me to take you to war. This is it.
德军在哪里
Then where are the Germans?
离这片无人区几百码开外的地方
Couple of 100 yards across the field.
-他们的战壕  -小心
- The trench is... - Watch out!
酋长  能见到您太好了
Chief! Oh it's good to see you.
酋长回来了  他回来了
Oi, chief's back! He's back!
好了  动身吧
Alright, let's move.
救命 请救救我
他们全抢走了
家 吃的
那些没逃出来的人
被当成了奴隶
在什么地方
费尔德 无人区的另一边
戴安娜  该走了
Diana, we have to go.
我们得帮助这些人
We need to help these people.
任务为重
We have to stay on mission!
下个据点至少还有一天的路
Next safe crossing is at least a day away.
磨磨蹭蹭干什么
What are we waiting for?
这些人快死了
We can not leave without helping them.
我们不能坐视不管
These people are dying.
食物短缺  村民被奴役
Nothing to eat and in the village enslaved it there!
我理解你的心情
I understand that.
妇女和孩子
Women and children!
我们得赶在日落前到达下一个据点
We need to make our next position by sunset.
怎么能这么说  你到底是怎么了
How can you say that? What is the matter with you?
这里是无人区  戴安娜
This is No Man's Land! Diana!
意味着没人能活着走过去
Means no man can cross it, alright?
军营在这里驻扎快一年了
This battalion has been here for nearly a year,
连一寸地都没攻下
and they barely gained an inch.
因为在另一头
Alright? Because on the other side,
一群德国人正端着机枪
there are a bunch of Germans pointing machine guns
瞄准这里每一寸土地
at every square inch of this place.
你根本不可能穿过去
This is not something you can cross. This is not possible.
所以呢  我们见死不救吗
So what? So we do nothing?
不  我们在救  只是
No, we are doing something. We are, we just...
史蒂夫
Steve.
我们救不了战争里的每一个人
We can't save everyone in this war.
史蒂夫
Steve, Steve
这不是我们的使命
This is not what we came here to do.
不
No,
这是我的使命
but it's what I'm going to do.
戴安娜
Diana!
这他妈演的是哪一出
What the bloody hell she's playing at?
有人来了  开火
Engage, fire!
她挡住了所有的火力  快冲
She's taking all the fire! Let's go!
别动  都别动
Stand down! Stand down!
这是命令
That's an order!
来吧
Come on!
她做到了  冲啊
She's done it! Let's go!
史蒂夫
Steve!
快走
Let's go!
Come on, go!
待着别动  我先过去
Stay here, I'll go ahead.
-这他妈  -走吧
- What the... - Let's move.
再来点火力
We need more firepower.
狙击手
Sniper!
快走
Move!
快进去
Get in!
查理  在钟楼上
Charlie, bell tower.
来吧  查理  开枪
Come on, Charlie. Shoot him.
放轻松
It's okay.
跟我来  掩护我
Follow me. Give me some cover.
好样的
Good!
把这个扛在背上
We're gonna put this on our back,
我说举  就立刻举起来
and when I say go, lift hard.
好
All right.
戴安娜  盾牌
Diana! Shield!
举
Go!
站稳不要动  朋友们
Stay very very still, for me my friends.
这很重要
Please. It's so important.
太谢谢你们了
Thank you very much.
能为你们拍照真是我的荣幸
This has been such an honor for me taking you photograph.
很感谢你们
Thank you so much.
嘴上说了那么久开枪
For all his talk of shooting,
他其实不会用枪
he cannot shoot.
不是每个人都能成为自己理想的样子
Not everyone gets to be where they want to be all the time.
我是个演员
Me, I'm an actor.
热爱表演
I love acting.
我才不想当士兵
I didn't want to be a soldier.
只可惜我生错了肤色
But I'm the wrong color.
人人都有自己的仗要打  戴安娜
Everyone's fighting their own battle, Diana.
就像你一样
Just like you're fighting yours.
太多了  真的
It's too much. I wish you...
谢谢您
Thank you.
我在打电话
Hi, I'm on the phone.
是费尔德
It's "Veld", V-E-L-D.
是个小村庄
It's a tiny village.
地图上可能找不到
It may not even be on the map.
费尔德
我找到了
I found it!
你找到鲁登道夫的实验室了吗
Did you find Ludendorff's operation?
还没有  但我能找到他
No. No, but I located him.
你运气真好  他离你只有几里路
And oh, lucky you, he's only a few miles away.
在德军最高指挥部
At German High Command.
德军最高指挥部
The German High Command?
根据情报
And to intel report,
鲁登道夫在举办宴会
Ludendorff is hosting a gala.
算是德军签署停战协定前最后的狂欢吧
Sort of a last hara before the Germans sign the armistice.
皇帝本人也会出席
And then the Kaiser himself is going to be there.
还有丸博士
As well as Dr. Maru.
宴会大概就是个幌子
Actually the Gala could be perfect cover.
-特雷弗上尉  -长官
- Captain Trevor. - Yes, sir.
明晚你决不允许
You're under no circumstances to go anywhere
去那个宴会  听见我的话了吗
near that gala tomorrow night. Do you hear me?
不然之前的努力就全白费了
You'll be jeopardizing everything we've worked for.
我们不能妨碍协定的签署
You can not compromise the armistice.
-德军一旦攻破前线  -史蒂夫
- Sir, there will be no armistice... - Steve!
停战协定也无从谈起了
once Ludendorff bombs the entire front line.
稍等我一下  长官
Hold on one second, sir.
我们不用担心停战协定的签署
We shouldn't be bothered about setting the peace agreement.
-为什么  -阿瑞斯绝不会
- Why not? - Ares would never let...
怎么了
What?
你想到什么了
What is that?
当然了  这才说得通啊
Of course, it makes complete sense.
阿瑞斯打造了一件终极武器
Ares developed a weapon, the worst ever devised.
-你说的是鲁登道夫吧  -不
- Ares? You mean Ludendorff. - No.
我说的就是阿瑞斯
I mean Ares.
鲁登道夫就是阿瑞斯
Ludendorff is Ares!
长官  这是我们最后的机会了
Sir, this is our last chance,
只有找到毒气藏在哪里
our final chance to find out where the gas is,
才能搞清楚鲁登道夫打算投放在哪
and to learn how Ludendorff plans on delivering it.
不行  我不许
No. I forbid it.
听到了吗  我不允许
Do you hear me? I forbid it.
长官  我这里信号不好
Sir, I am losing you! Sir?
-什么  -长官
- Hello? - Sir...
他有多大几率会听我的话
How likely is he to respect my wishes?
约等于零
Not very like, I'm convinced.
萨米  别这样
Sammy, Sammy, no, no.
我还有工作要做
Sammy, I have to work.
为了明天的宴会
I gotta rustle up with a German uniform
我还得搞一套德军军服
I took to plot the course tomorrow.
这还不简单  来吧
That's easy, boss. Come on.
反正天亮前我们也做不了什么
There's nothing we can do till tomorrow.
你自己说的  史蒂夫
You said yourself, Steve.
-谢谢您  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
你做到了
You did this.
是我们
We did.
你以前在天堂岛
Do you have dancing on
跳过舞吗
Paradise Island?
当然跳过了
Oh, dancing, yeah of course.
这些人就是摇来摇去而已
These people are just... swaying.
考虑到你要对抗的是战争之神
Okay, if you're gonna be fighting the God of war,
我就勉为其难地教教你跳舞吧
I might as well teach you how to dance, you poor thing.
枪是不需要的
Alright, probably without the gun.
赏脸跳个舞吗
If you would...
这个嘛
Well...
要去宴会的话  我得学学你们的舞蹈了
If I'm going to a Gala, I'll need to know how to dance.
-你不能去宴会  -我当然要去
- You aren't going to the Gala. - Of course I am.
-不行  -为什么
- No. - Why wouldn't I?
首先  你不会跳舞
Well, for one, you don't know how to dance.
我还可以说他们不会跳舞呢
I would argue with this, they don't know how to dance.
虚心点
Be polite.
来吧  手给我
All right. Give me your hand.
像这样
Like so.
我会用手臂
And I'll put my arm
搂着你
around you like so.
然后就
And we just...
那叫什么  摇来摇去吗
What you call? Sway?
我们就摇来摇去
We'll just sway.
你靠得太近了
You're awfully close.
这才是跳舞的意义
That's this all about.
好吧
I see.
我会与你并肩 走遍这个世界
美梦 乐曲和鲜花将围绕着你
好些年没听他唱歌了
I haven't heard him sing in years.
我要凝视你的双眼 握紧你的手
我会与你并肩 走过黄金宝地
这叫下雪
It's a snowfall.
碰碰看
Touch it.
真神奇
It's magical!
对吧
It is, isn't it?
是很神奇
Yes, yeah.
没有战争的时候  人们都这样生活吗
Is this what people do when there are no wars to fight?
对啊
Yeah.
还会做些别的事
Yeah, this... and other things.
什么事
What things?
吃早餐
They have breakfast.
人们可喜欢吃早餐了
They really love a breakfast.
还有起床之后
And they love to wake up,
看看报纸  然后去上班
read the paper and go to work.
以后还会结婚
They get married.
生个小孩然后白头偕老
Makes some babies and grow old together.
我是这么想的
I guess.
那是什么样的
What is that like?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
村民们送的马
The villagers gave them to us.
-馈赠啊  -他们还称我们为英雄
- A gracious gift. - And they call us heroes.
你是啊
You are.
那个  兄弟们
Hey, fellas, I know that
我说过这是两天的任务
I said this job was 2 day's,
现在两天到了  说话算话
and a deal is a deal.
没我们你撑不过去的
You can't last without us.
是啊
Yeah.
戴安娜倒是能保护好自己
We all know Diana is capable of taking care of herself.
我担心的是你
I'm worried that you won't make it.
没有赏金了
No more money.
之前的够了
We have been paid enough.
没了我你们更好
You will be better off without me.
不  查理
No, Charlie.
谁唱歌给我们啊
Who will sing for us?
-对啊  -这就算了
- Yeah. - Oh no, please.
唱歌
Sing?
这是你自找的
You asked for it.
绿色蔓延 一望无边
芦苇苍苍
The reeds are green.
绿野莽莽
绿色蔓延 一望无边
我曾经度过的 最美好的时光
我生命中最美妙的时光
The sweetest hours I could live.
你当我是小孩吗
You must think I was born yesterday.
听起来很疯狂  但是是真的
I know it sounds crazy, but it's true.
千真万确
Every word.
等一下  等一下
Wait. Wait. Wait.
你说一座岛上全是像她一样的女人
There is a whole island of women like her?
然后一个男的也没有吗
And not a single man among them?
告诉我怎么去
How do we get there?
然后她认为
And she thinks..
鲁登道夫就是战争之神阿瑞斯
...that Ludendorff is Ares, the god of war?
只有杀了他才能结束战争
And only by killing him will the war end.
少唬我了
Don't be daft.
可你当时都看见了
You saw what happened out there.
毫发无伤地端掉重机枪
The way she dropped that machine gun nest.
攻下了那座钟楼
The way she took out the tower?
说不定是真的呢
May be it's true.
我觉得是真的
I think it's true.
我也相信是真的
I believe it's true.
史蒂夫  你该不会也相信这些瞎扯吧
Steven son, you don't really believe those rubbish thing?
戴安娜  注意隐蔽
Diana, Diana, hiding.
这要怎么才能进去
How the hell do we get into that?
门口的几个守卫很好引开
I see only a couple of guards in the door to distract.
是啊  我这么大摇大摆过去
Yeah, it won't look suspicious
看上去真的一点也不可疑呢
when I wanna come sauntering out of the woods.
我能过去
I could get in.
不行  太危险了
You are not going in there, it's too dangerous.
-危险  -对啊
- Too dangerous? - Yes, too dangerous.
而且你这一身太招摇了
And you are too distracting.
我先进去
I will go in there,
看看能不能顺藤摸瓜
follow them to find where they are working on the gas.
找到毒气厂的位置
Or better yet, where it is.
-我和你一起去  -不行
- I'm coming with you. - No, you are not coming with me.
你的衣服不适合当卧底
What you're wearing isn't exactly undercover.
我觉得吧
I don't know.
她很适合在宴会里边当卧底
I would say she was pretty undercover on that battlefield.
我们不能带你过去
It's just gonna, we can't get you there.
就是去探探情报就回来了
It's all scouted out, we'll put back...
只要他还活着就不可能
But as long as he's still alive, it doesn't...
硬闯的话不可能不杀人
You cannot go in there and not kill anyone.
行不通的  相信我吧
You just can't. You have to trust me.
这是哪儿搞来的
Where did that come from?
我能开吗  让我来驾驶好不好
Can I drive it? Please let me drive it!
我来当你的司机
Yes, I'll be your chauffeur.
走吧走吧
Come on.
待着别动
Stay put!
你从哪儿搞来的
Where did this come from?
那边那里  全是这种车
A field over there. It is full of them!
酋长  我们得熟悉一下地形
Chief, I think you and me scope out the area,
以便我们进可攻退可守
in case we need to beat the haste and retreat.
你觉得呢  戴安娜
What do you say, Diana?
上校
Colonel.
史蒂夫  他们有邀请函
Steve, they have invitations.
别怕  冷静  你可以的
Do not worry. Play it cool, you go this, you got this.
能看看您的邀请函吗
Your invitation, please.
上校和我将为你送上衷心的问候
The Colonel and I wish many blessings and all my love
和诚挚的祝福
to fall up in your head.
你脑子里都装了些什么
Your head must be empty.
快找邀请函  白痴
Find my invitation, you idiot.
抱歉  十分抱歉
I am sorry. I am so sorry.
我千不该万不该  我的主人
I must apologize a thousand times, my master.
我犯了一个最可怕  最不可饶恕的错误
I made the most horrible, the most unforgivable mistake.
-邀请函被我弄丢了  -你说什么
- I lost the Colonel's invitation. - What?
你是说我们一路颠簸到这里来
You saying we come all the way through the mud and rain,
你把邀请函给我颠丢了
only for you to loose my invitation?
我捅娄子了
No, I am a bug.
我捅天大的娄子了  我就是个臭虫
Not even a bug, I'm a dung of a bug.
主人您说得对
And you're right master...
神会保佑您的
Blessing will upon us.
这也太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
我可不要在这里耗一整晚
I'm not gonna be spending my evening out here.
你个蠢货  车快开走啊
You stupid idiots! Move your car!
你这穿的都是些什么呀
What are you supposed to be?
你要干什么
What are you doing?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我不喝酒
I don't drink.
我们见过吗
Have we met?
没有  可我注意你很久了
No, but I have been watching you.
持续关注着你的事业
Following your career.
你就是伊莎贝尔·丸博士
You are Dr. Isabel Maru.
德军里最天赋异凛的化学家
The most talented chemist in the German army.
我是你的崇拜者
I am a fan.
无意冒犯
I hope I'm not crossing a line.
我知道你和鲁登道夫将军
I know you and General Ludendorff are
走得很近
very close.
我们只是一起共事
We work well together. Yes.
像我这样默默在背后注视你的人
Tell me someone like me behind you...
可以给你更多
I could provide a lot more.
你是谁
And who are you?
一个配得上你才华的倾慕者
A man who shows you appreciation a genius like yourself deserves.
我很喜欢火  你呢
I love fire, don't you?
我觉得它是
It is like,
有序趋向无序的最佳体现
a living act of entropy.
毁灭世界的终极武器
The ultimate weapon of destruction.
提醒着我们  到了最后
Reminding us that in the end.
也不过是尘归尘  土归土
Everything eventually returns to the ash it came from.
听着不禁使人感到宽慰
There is something reassuring about it.
我在你眼中看到了这一切
I see all of that in your eyes.
也许你可以给我看看你的研究
Perhaps you could show me what you're working on.
我听说
I hear it is...
我听说很厉害
I hear it is extraordinary.
很谢谢你对我的研究那么感兴趣
I appreciate your interest in my work.
不过我对鲁登道夫将军很忠诚
But I'm loyal to General Ludendorff.
除此之外
Besides,
我已经知道你的注意力在
now I see your attention is,
别处
elsewhere.
在派对上玩得开心吗
Enjoying the party?
我并不太清楚我们在庆祝什么
I confess I'm not sure what it is we're celebrating.
当然是德军的胜利
A German victory, of course.
胜利
Victory?
但是我听说和平很快要到来了
But I hear peace would be so close.
和平
Peace?
只会有个破停战协定
It's only an armistice.
和永不休止的战争
And an endless war.
修西得底斯
Thucydides.
你还懂古希腊人物啊
You know your ancient Greeks?
他们明白
They understood,
战争是一个神
that war was a god.
他需要人类去作出牺牲
A god who requires human sacrifices.
作为交换
And in exchange,
战争让人类找到了目标和意义
war gives man purpose, meaning,
一个超越卑微自我的机会
a chance to rise above his petty, mortal little self.
变得更加有胆识  更高贵  更优秀
And be courageous, noble, better!
众神中只有一位对此坚信不疑
Only one of the many gods believed in that.
但他是错的
And he was wrong.
你一点都不了解神
You know nothing of the gods.
将军先生
Herr General.
好好享受烟火
Enjoy the fireworks.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
-别挡路  -戴安娜  看着我
- Out of my way! - Diana, look at me.
如果在找到毒气之前杀了鲁登道夫
If you kill Ludendorff before we find the gas.
我们就阻止不了任何事
We won't be able to stop anything.
我会阻止阿瑞斯
I will stop Ares!
如果你是错的呢
What if you're wrong?
如果根本就没有什么阿瑞斯呢
What if there's no Ares?
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
我不能让你这样做
I can not let you do this.
我做什么与你无关
What I do is not up to you.
戴安娜
Diana!
Diana.
毒气
The gas.
村民们
The villagers!
他们为什么在欢呼
What they cheering for?
戴安娜
Diana!
他们发射了什么
What did they fire?
毒气
The gas.
是鲁登道夫
It was Ludendorff.
我看到他了  他在塔上
I saw him, he was in the tower.
他无论去哪里你都要跟着
Wherever he goes you follow.
你要怎么找到我们
How will you find us?
我有办法
I know how.
戴安娜
Diana!
他们死了  他们都死了
They are dead. They are all dead.
我本可以救活他们的
I could have saved them.
如果不是因为你  我可以救活他们的
I could have saved them if it weren't for you.
你阻止我去杀阿瑞斯
You stopped me from killing Ares!
-不  -放开我
- No! - Get away from me!
我已经懂了
I understand everything now.
被阿瑞斯蛊惑的不仅仅是德国人
It isn't just the Germans that Ares has corrupted.
还有你
It's you too.
你们所有人
All of you.
我会找到阿瑞斯
I'll find Ares.
我会杀了他
And I'll kill him.
戴安娜
Diana!
那烟
That smoke.
是酋长
It's the chief!
他在追踪鲁登道夫
He followed Ludendorff.
跟着那烟
Follow the smoke!
戴安娜  在那边
Hey! Diana, Over there!
我们走吧
Come on. Let's go!
真是意外啊
What a surprise.
奇怪了
Strange.
很不幸  我还有一个地方要去
Unfortunately, I have another matter to attend to.
你是什么
What are you?
很快你就会知道了
You will soon find out.
尽管你很厉害  但还不是我的对手
As magnificent as you are, you are still no match for me.
我们等着瞧吧
We'll see about that.
我是天堂岛的戴安娜
I am Diana Temiscira.
亚马逊人的女王
Daughter of Hippolyta.
希波吕忒的女儿
Queen of the Amazons.
你毁灭世界的怒火熄灭吧
And your wrath upon this world is over.
以这个世界的一切善良为名
In the name of all that it is good in this world.
我要完成亚马逊人的使命
I hereby complete the mission of the Amazons.
让你在这个世界永远消失
To ridding this world of you forever!
戴安娜
Diana?
Diana!
我杀死了他
I killed him.
我杀死了他  但一切还在继续
I killed him, but nothing stops.
如果杀了战争之神  战争就会结束
If you kill the god of war, you stop the war.
这正是我们的当务之急
Exactly what we have to do now.
我们必须阻止毒气的释放  赶紧
We must stop the gas. Come on.
不  这一切理应结束
No. All this should have stopped.
戴安娜
Diana.
战争应该要结束了  为什么没有
The fighting should have stopped. Why are they?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know! I don't know.
阿瑞斯已死
Ares is dead.
他们不用再打了
They can stop fighting now.
为什么他们还要继续打
Why are they still fighting?
也许他们本性如此
Because maybe it's them!
也许
Maybe...
也许人类并不都是善良的
Maybe people aren't always good.
有没有阿瑞斯都一样
Ares or no Ares.
也许人类本身就那样
Maybe it's just, who they are.
-戴安娜  -不
- Diana - No.
戴安娜  这些我们可以等会再聊
Diana, we can talk about this later.
-我需要你跟我来  -不
- I need you to come with me. - No, no!
经历了这么多  这不可能
After everything I saw, it can't be!
不可能是那样的
Can not be!
他们在自相残杀
They were killing each other.
杀害那些他们看不到的人  孩子
Killing people they cannot see. Children.
孩子啊
Children!
一定是因为阿瑞斯  而不是他们
No, it had to be him. It can not be them!
戴安娜  人类  我
Diana, people... I...
她说得对
She was right.
我母亲说得对
My mother was right.
她说人类不值得我去拯救
She said the world of men do not deserve you.
他们不值得我们去拯救  史蒂夫
They don't deserve our help, Steve.
-与值不值得无关  -他们不值得我们去救
- It's not about deserve! - They do not deserve our help.
也许我们不值得
Maybe...maybe we don't!
但跟那没关系  一切取决于你相信什么
But it's not about that. It's about what you believe.
我经历了那么多  你以为我还不懂吗
You don't think I get it, after what I've seen out there?
你以为我不想告诉你
You don't think I wish I could tell you
这全都是一个人的错吗
that there was one bad guy to blame?
但不是的
It's not!
我们都有错
We are all to blame.
我没有
I am not.
但或许我有错
But maybe I am!
求你了
Please.
如果你相信这场战争必须停止
If you believe that this war should stop...
如果你想阻止这场战争
If you want to stop it.
现在就帮我一起阻止它
Help me stop it right now.
因为
Because...
如果你不帮忙  还会有上千人死亡
If you don't, there will kill thousands more.
求你了  跟我来吧
Please, please come with me.
我必须得走
I have to go.
-戴安娜呢  -我们只能靠自己了
- Where is Diana? - We are on our own.
-什么  -你看到什么了  查理
- What? - What did you see, Charlie?
好像就是一堆气泵
Seems like a bunch of gas pumps.
但是我看不到他们要运去哪里
But I can't see where they're taking them.
我们要怎么混进去
How are we gonna get in there?
我有个办法  跟我来
I have got an idea. Come on guys.
跟上
Come on!
谁在那里
Who's there?
帕特里克长官
Sir Patrick.
你是对的  戴安娜
You were right, Diana.
他们不值得我们去拯救
They don't deserve our help.
他们只配得上毁灭
They only deserve destruction.
你
You.
你是他
You are him.
就是我
I am.
但我并不是你想的那样
But I'm not what you thought I was.
那是什么
What is that?
未来
Future.
我不是你的敌人  戴安娜
I'm not your enemy, Diana.
我是唯一一个真正了解你的人
I'm the only one who truly knows you.
也像你一样  看透了人类
And who truly knows them, as you now do.
人类一直这样  也永远这样
They always been and always will be
懦弱  残忍  自私
weak, cruel, selfish
能干出最可怕的事
and capable of the greatest horrors.
我一直以来都希望
All I ever wanted was
众神能看到我父亲创造的人类有多邪恶
for the Gods to see how evil my father's creation was.
但他们拒绝了
But they refused.
我是戴安娜·舍密斯盖拉
I am Diana Temiscira.
所以我毁灭了他们
So I destroyed them.
希波吕忒的女儿
Daughter of Hippolyta.
我是来完成她的
And I am here to complete her...
弑神者
The God Killer.
我亲爱的孩子
My dear Child.
那不是弑神者
That's not the God Killer.
你才是
You are.
只有神才能杀死神
Only a God can kill another God.
宙斯和亚马逊女王生下了他们的孩子
Zeus left the child he had with the queen of the Amazon.
作为对抗我的武器
As a weapon to use against me.
不  你这个骗子
No. You liar.
我命令你告诉我真相
I compel you to tell me the truth.
我说的就是真相
I am.
我不是战争之神  戴安娜
I'm not the god of war, Diana.
我是真理之神
I am the God of truth.
人类
Mankind.
从我们的手上偷走了这个世界
Stole this world from us.
日复一日  他们在摧毁它
They ruined it, day by day.
而只有我看透了这一切
And I, the only one wise enough to see it,
却太弱而无法阻止他们
was left too weak to stop them.
这么多年以来  我只好孤军奋战
All these years I have struggled alone.
在他们耳边低语
Whispering into their ears.
告诉他们想法  配方的灵感
Ideas, inspiration for forms,
制造武器
Weapons.
但我没有让他们去使用
But I don't make them used them.
战争都是他们自己挑起的
They start these wars on their own.
我只需要安排一个停战协议
All I do is orchestrate an armistice
我知道他们无法不自相残杀
I know they cannot keep in the hope that they destroy themselves.
但让他们自相残杀还不够
But it is never been enough.
伦敦
直到你的出现
Until you.
当你第一次出现时  我本打算摧毁你
When you first arrived I was going to crush you.
但是我知道  如果你能看到
But I knew that if only you could see
众神所看不到的东西
what the other gods could not.
你就会想加入我  而我们强强联手的话
Then you would join me, and with our powers combined.
我们就可以结束所有的痛苦
We could finally end all the pain, all the suffering.
他们带来的破坏
Destruction they bring.
我们就可以将这个世界
And we could return this world
恢复成以前的天堂
to the paradise it was before them.
永远
Forever.
我
I...
我永远也不可能与你为伍
I can never be a part of that.
亲爱的  我不想跟你打
My dear, I don't want to fight you.
但如果真的有这个必要
But if I must.
-史蒂夫  -我们走吧
- Steve! - Come on, let's go!
萨米  我们走吧
Sammy, let's go!
把这些东西给我弄走
Get these things out of here.
亲爱的  你还有很多东西要学
Oh my dear, you have so much to learn.
天啊
Oh my God!
我们要怎么办
What are we gonna do?
如果那真的是战争之神
There is not much we can do
那么我们也无计可施了
if that's who I think it is.
但是我们可以阻止飞机起飞
But we can stop that plane.
如果我们能连上无线电
If we could get on the radio,
我们可以让空军将它打下来
we can ask flying corp to shoot her down.
不行  如果飞机坠毁
No. If it crashes,
方圆50平方英里内的人都会遭殃
it will wipe everyone out for 50 square miles.
我们不能让它起飞
We gotta ground it!
坏消息  上面有计时器
Bad news. It is on a timer.
如果我们不让它起飞  还是会泄露
If we ground it here, it's the same thing.
这个是易燃的吗  酋长
Is it flammable, Chief?
你说是氢化物  所以是易燃的
Yes, you said it's hydrogen. It's flammable.
你们给我开条道  我要到飞机上去
I need you guys to clear me a path to that plane.
-不要  史蒂夫  -史蒂夫
- No, Steve! - Hey, Steve!
跟紧点
Come on!
快过来  这边  史蒂夫
Come on! This way! Steve!
-赶紧  史蒂夫  -快快快
- Come on, Steve. - Ahead! Go!
史蒂夫
Steve!
来看看你这个神有多少能耐
Let's see what kind of god you really are.
你会帮我毁灭他们的  戴安娜
You will help me destroy them, Diana.
不然你也会赔上小命
Or you will die.
快快快  赶紧走
Come on! Move, move, let's go! Go. Go. Go.
-跟紧跟紧  -赶紧往前跑
- Progress! Come on! - Ahead! Run!
你就这点能耐吗
Is that all you have to offer?
你是不可能赢的
It is futile to imagine you can win.
放弃吧  戴安娜
Give up, Diana.
酋长  还有弹药吗
Chief! Anything left?
没了
I got nothing.
-什么都行  -没了
- Anything! - No!
史蒂夫
Steve.
不
No!
没错  戴安娜
Yes, Diana!
把他们都杀了
Take them all!
你终于明白了
Finally you see.
看看这个世界
Look at this world.
这一切都是人类造成的  与我无关
Mankind did this, not me.
他们丑陋
They are ugly.
满腔怒火
Filled with hatred.
懦弱无能
Weak.
跟你的特雷弗上尉一样
Just like your captain Trevor.
连死都没有为你留下什么
Gone and left you nothing.
这是为了什么
And for what?
可悲
Pathetic!
他活该被烧死
He deserved to burn!
看着她  然后告诉我  我是错的
Look at her and tell me I'm wrong.
她就是这些人类中最典型的例子
She is the perfect example of these humans.
完全不值得你的同情
And unworthy of your sympathy in every way.
毁了她  戴安娜
Destroy her, Diana.
你知道那是她活该  他们都活该
You know that she deserves. And they all do.
动手
Do it!
戴安娜
Diana!
Diana.
什么
What?
我要走了
I have to go.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
史蒂夫
Steve.
无论是什么  我都可以做到
Whatever it is, I can do it.
不
No.
-让我来  -不
- Let me do it. - No.
一定得是我
It has to be me.
我来拯救今天  你来拯救世界
I can save today. You can save the world.
我希望我们有更多的时间
I wish we had more time.
什么  你在说什么
What? What are you saying?
我爱你
I love you!
你对他们的看法是错的
You are wrong about them.
他们的确像你所说那样
They are everything you say.
但不仅如此
But so much more.
谎言
Lies!
他们不值得你的保护
They do not deserve your protection!
与值不值得无关
It's not about deserving.
关键是你相信什么
It's about what you believe.
而我相信爱
And I believe in love.
那就让我毁了你吧
Then I will destroy you!
再见了  哥哥
Goodbye brother.
伟大的战争
结束了
过去我总想着拯救世界
I used to want to save the world.
结束战争  给人类带来和平
To end war and bring peace to mankind.
后来我瞥见到那所谓的光明中潜藏的黑暗
But then I glimpsed the darkness that lives within their light,
意识到原来在每个人心中
and learned that inside every one of them,
永远都有善恶两面
there will always be both.
每个人都需要自己作出抉择
A choice each must make for themselves.
这是任何英雄都无法代劳的
Something no hero will ever defeat.
现在我终于知道
And now I know,
只有爱能真正拯救世界
that only love can truly save the world.
所以我留下来了
So I stay.
我为之抗争  付出
I fight and I give.
致布鲁斯·韦恩：
感谢你把他带回我身边.
为了自己心中那美好的世界
For the world I know can be.
这是我现在的使命
This is my mission now.
直到永远
Forever.
无聊老生制作  谢谢各位观赏
导演
派蒂·杰金斯
编剧
阿伦·海伯格
故事
扎克·施奈德  阿伦·海 伯格 杰森·福克斯
制片人
查尔斯·罗文
黛博拉·施奈德  扎克·施奈德
制片人
理查德·萨克尔
执行制片人
戈夫·约翰斯  乔恩·贝格
韦斯利·科勒 瑞贝卡·斯蒂尔· 罗文
执行制片人
史蒂芬·琼斯
联合制片人
汤米·戈姆利  寇蒂斯·凯尼摩托
改编授权版权方ＤＣ漫画
神奇女侠 角色原创 威廉·莫尔顿·马斯顿
摄影指导
马修·詹森
艺术指导
阿莱恩·博内托
影片剪辑
马丁·沃尔什
视觉特效
比尔·威斯登霍佛
电影配乐
鲁伯特·格雷格森·威特廉斯
服装设计
林迪·海明
联合制片人
劳拉·肯尼迪  克斯蒂·卡尔森  露辛达·锡森
盖尔·加朵
克里斯·派恩
罗宾·莱特
康妮·尼尔森
大卫·休里斯
丹尼·休斯顿
埃琳纳·安娜亚
艾文·布莱纳
露茜·戴维斯
丽莎·洛文·孔斯利
萨伊德·塔格马奥
尤金·布雷·洛克
华纳兄弟电影公司 荣誉出品
拉特派克-沙丘娱乐  腾讯电影公司  万达电影公司
携手献映
阿特拉斯娱乐 / 酷卓制片 承制
神奇女侠